Harry Stewart papers, 1930-1979
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Harry Stewart papers, 1930-1979
MS 394
Harry Stewart
Papers, 1930-1979. Papers of bookseller and curator Harry Stewart. Papers include correspondence relating to book trade and personal life, catalogs relating to western paraphernalia, material from the New Mexico College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts, notes, and photocopies of news clippings with photographs featuring Harry Stewart.
0.5 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Biographical Note
Harry Stewart was a book dealer specializing in Western history. He operated businesses in Boise, Idaho, and Tucson and Tombstone, Arizona, where he was also curator of the Wyatt Earp Museum.
Organization
This collection is organized into five series.
Series I: Correspondence, 1940-1973
Series II: Catalogs, ca. 1950s-1970s
Series III: Notes, ca. 1960s
Series IV: Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1979
Series V: New Mexico College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts, 1930-1942
Scope and Content Note
Papers of bookseller and curator Harry Stewart. Papers include correspondence relating to book trade and personal life, catalogs relating to western paraphernalia, material from the New Mexico College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts, notes, and news clippings with photographs featuring Harry Stewart. Includes correspondence from Otto Perry, railroad photographer.
Access Terms
Stewart, Harry C.-Archives.
Perry, Otto, 1894-1970-Correspondence.
New Mexico College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts.-Agricultural Experiment Station.
Booksellers and bookselling-Southwest, New.
Catalogs, Booksellers'.
Cattle-Feeding and feeds.
Range management-New Mexico.
Container List
- Series I: Correspondence, 1940-1973
  - Subseries 1.1: Business, 1946-1973
    - Business A - F, 1947-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Business G - L, 1950-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Business M - P, 1946-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Business R - Y, 1948-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 1.2: Personal, 1940-1971
    - Personal, 1940-1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Series II: Catalogs, ca. 1950s-1970s
  - Catalogs, ca. 1950s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Series III: Notes, ca. 1960s
  - Notes, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Series IV: Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1979
  - Newspaper clippings (Photocopies), 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Series V: New Mexico College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts, 1930-1942
  - Press Bulletins, 1930-1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1936-1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)